50年前著名民权运动领袖马丁路德金先生 在华盛顿特区林肯纪念堂前发表了著名演讲 《我有一个梦想》
...the famous speech I have a Dream at the Lincoln Memorior, Washington D.C.
今晚在这里 纽约时代广场 一个来自中国大陆的年轻人
Tonight here Time Square New York City a young man coming from China
将发表演讲《梦想的力量》
will deliver a new speech The Power of Dream
当人类文明的自由之光普照美国 普照全世界的时候
While the American people are enjoying the shine of liberty
在古老的东方中国大陆依然是落后野蛮的独裁统治
In mainland China millions of Chinese have no human rights
很难想象 今时今日 中国大陆的13亿人民仍没有言论自由
It's hard to imagine that at this moment 1.3 billion Chinese citizens have no freedom of speech
我们不能批评政府
We can't say anything about the government
我们只允许辛苦工作 不停纳税
We have to work hard and pay high taxes
但我们从来没有见过选票
But we have never a ballot
我们是人 但我们没有人权
We are human beings but we have no human rights
中国是警察国家
China is a police country
现在我们需要改变
Now we need a change
我们需要抗争
We need to fight
我们需要行动
We need action
今晚我们在这里
Tonight we stand here
为自由呐喊 因为我们有一个梦想
shouting for freedom because we have a dream
我们相信梦想就是力量
and we belive that dream is power
当1989年中共政府用机枪和坦克屠杀市民和学生的时候
When the Chinese government killed thousands of students in Beijing 1989
这个政权的合法性已经不复存在
they have lost our trust
中国政府是骗子
The Chinese government is a liar
中国政府是屠夫
The Chinese government is a killer
中国政府是杀人犯
The Chinese government is a murderer
所以 我们需要建立一个民有民治民享的新政府
So we need to build a new government of the people by the people and for the people
在每个人的心中都有一个梦想
In everyone's heart there is a dream
一个有一天所有人在我们可爱的祖国 中国 享受自由生活的梦想
the dream that one day we can enjoy our freedom of life in our beloved country China
我们爱祖国
We love the country
我们爱中华
We love the nation
我们爱神州大地
We love the land
我们希望不久的将来 中国实行民主化
We wish in the near future China will be a democratic country
因为梦想 我们更加强大
Because of dream we have more power
因为梦想 我们永不放弃
Because of dream we never give  up
因为梦想 我们拥有自由
Because of dream we enjoy liberty and freedom
因为梦想 我们将改变世界
Because of dream we will change the world
因为梦想 我们创造未来
Because of dream we will build the new future
自由中国
Free free China
民主中国
Democracy China
人权中国
Humanrights China
释放刘晓波
Release Liu Xiaobo
释放王炳章
Free free Wang Bingzhang
释放朱一波（音）
Free free Zhu Yibo
释放郭泉
Free free Guo Quan
释放程卫（音）
Free free Chen Wei
释放程欣（音)
Free free Chen Xin
释放许志永
Free free Xu Zhiyong
释放郭飞雄
Free free Guo Feixiong
释放丁家喜
Free free Ding Jiaxi
释放赵常青
Free free Zhao Changqing
释放所有政治犯
Free free everyone
结束一党专政
建立民主中国
打到贪官污吏
中国属于人民
开放党禁
开放报禁
开放网禁
言论自由
结社自由
信仰自由
游行自由
示威自由
司法独立
军队国家化
自由中国
Freedom China
谢谢
Thank you
[字幕制作  每日油兔 2018.1.24]